https://footballguys.com/fbgprivacy.php

Special Mid Season Discounts
We save you time and help you win. You'll know who to start, sit, drop, add, and trade. Check out our Mid Season Discounts.
Auction Drafts
Daily Fantasy (DFS)
FFPC & FPC
Individual DefensivePlayers (IDP)
Multi Lineup Optimizer Quick Start Guide
IMPORTANT NOTE: The Single Lineup Builder replaces the old Interactive Value Charts (IVCs). We combined the IVC features you love with mobile-friendly updates that many subscribers requested.
Week 14 NFL Daily Fantasy Features
Top DFS Content
DFS Videos
Sports Wagering
General NFL Features
NFL Stats
DFS Archives
News
Player Stats
Historical Stats (1996-)
Target Stats (2002-)
Number of Top Fantasy Finishes
Team Stats
Game Logs
Team Stats
Target Details
Redzone Stats
Stats Searches
Data Dominator (2002-)
Game Log Dominator (1995-)
Historical Data Dominator (1960-)
IDP Matchup Analyzer (2003-)
Tools
League Dominator
Edit/Sync Your Leagues
5-Second Primer
Matchup Dominator
Roster Analysis
Week 14 Rankings
Waiver Wire Report
Multi Lineup Optimizer Quick Start Guide
IMPORTANT NOTE: The Single Lineup Builder replaces the old Interactive Value Charts (IVCs). We combined the IVC features you love with mobile-friendly updates that many subscribers requested.
2020 Draft Dominator
Draft Dominator Online
Draft Dominator Mobile
Draft DominatorQuick Start Guide
Start a Mock Draft
Draft Dominator Classicfor Windows
Draft Dominator Classicfor Mac
Other 2020 Draft Tools
Forum Registration
Shark Pool (NFL Talk)
Daily Fantasy Sports
Footballguys Players Championship
The Assistant Coach
Mock Drafts R Us
Looking For Leagues
IDP Forum
IDP Assistant Coach
Baseball
2021 Subscriber Contest - Postseason
2021 Contest(Coming January 2021)
2020 Postseason Rules
2021 Footballguys Playoff Challenge
2021 Challenge(Coming January 2021)
2020 Playoff Rules
MyFBG
League Dominator
Edit/Sync Your Leagues
5-Second Primer
Matchup Dominator
Roster Analysis
Week 14 Rankings
Special Mid Season Discounts
We save you time and help you win. You'll know who to start, sit, drop, add, and trade. Check out our Mid Season Discounts.
Footballguys.com Privacy Policy
Last Updated: 4/20/2015
Footballguys.com is dedicated to providing all the fantasy football information that you need to DOMINATE YOUR LEAGUE.
We're constantly working on new features and tools to keep you, our subscribers, better informed.
We also realize that privacy is a very important issue to our site visitors and subscribers.
This Privacy Policy details what type of information we collect on our visitors and how it is used.
Personally Identifying Information
We collect the Personally Identifying Information listed below:
Signing Up For Subscriber Site:
When purchasing a subscription from Footballguys, we ask for your name, an email address, a username, and a password.
We also store the IP address that the subscription request came from for security.
We only collect information on your physical address if you order a product that requires that we ship it to you by mail.
We do not collect or retain any payment information such as credit card numbers, bank account numbers or PINs -- our payment processor (currently PayPal) handles this for us.
The only payment information we retain is the receipt number on the transaction that our payment processor sends to us.
Signing Up For Message Board:
When registering for the Footballguys Message Board, we ask for a username, a password, an email address, and your time zone.
We also store the IP address that the registration request was made from so that we can detect and manage duplicate accounts.
We do not require any other information to set up a message board account.
Logging In To Subscriber Site:
When you log in to the Subscriber Site, we ask for your login and password.
We also collect your IP address so that we can extract and analyze demographic data about our subscribers.
Logging In To Message Board:
When you log in to the Message Board, we ask for your Message Board login and password.
No other information is stored when you log in to the Message Board.
Using The Subscriber Site:
Each time you access Subscriber Content, we record your login and IP address.
We record this information so that we can determine how popular each of our tools and features are and so that we can detect login sharing.
Using the Message Board:
Each time you post a new topic, reply to an existing topic, or vote in a poll on the message board, your username, IP address, and the content of your topic, reply, or vote are stored in our database.
We store this data because it provides the content of the Message Board itself and the identity of the user who created it.
Cookies
Footballguys uses cookies to recognize and remember the identities of our registered users so that they do not have to log in each time they return to the site.
We also use cookies on our Message Board to store some user preferences such as the number of messages or topics to display on a page, topics already read, etc. A "cookie" is a small text file containing letters or numbers that is sent to your computer when you visit a website.
Most browsers accept cookies by default. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent. However, some Footballguys features or services may not function correctly if cookies cannot be set to your browser.
Information sharing
We do not provide, rent, or sell any of your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals.
If you have an account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies.
We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which Sportsguys, LLC. or its agents maintain facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country.
In the event of a transfer of ownership of Sportsguys, LLC., such as acquisition by or merger with another company, we will provide notice before any personally identifying information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
We may share aggregated information with others. Examples of this include how many users clicked on a particular advertisement.
We will not provide the individual identities of users in this case.
Information security
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.
We provide access to your personally identifying information only to a minimum number of our employees who need to know that information in order to provide service to our customers or develop and improve our services.
Updating your information
We provide webpages where you may update and correct your personally identifying information.
On our Message Boards, click on the "My Controls" link for more information.
On our Subscriber Site, visit this page.
External links
Any external sites linked from pages on Footballguys.com are created and maintained by people and companies we have no control over. These other sites are not bound by our Privacy Policy and they may have different policies regarding the collection of personal information, cookies, etc.
Email updates
Footballguys.com does not send unsolicited mail.
We send news updates during the offseason to people who subscribe to our offseason mailing list.
During the season, we send selected content and breaking news updates to our subscribers by email.
If you do not wish to receive these messages, you can unsubscribe from the mailing list by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the email, by visiting this page, or by sending an email to subscription@footballguys.com.
We do not share the membership list of our mailing lists with anyone.
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
Footballguys.com believes that it is particularly important to protect the privacy of children. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our web sites from those we actually know are under the age of 13, and no part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.
Changes to this Policy
Our Privacy Policy will change from time to time as we expand our services to our subscribers. We believe that most changes will be minor, but there may be more substantial changes at some point in the future. In any case, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notification of the change. We will place the effective date of each Privacy Policy at the top of this page. Prior versions of this Privacy Policy will be kept in an archive for you to view.
Privacy Policy Archive
Effective date: 3/21/2009
If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us at any time.
subscription@footballguys.com
Footballguys.com
PO Box 937
Cabot, AR 72023-0937
Join the FBG Family
Buy Now
Money Back Guarantee
Testimonials
Popular Features
#Trendspotting: Week 14 - Zamichieli
Injury Expectations | Midweek Update | Week 14 - Bramel
Week 14 Sleepers - Bloom
Roundtable Week 14 - Staff
Upgrades, Downgrades, and Waiver Wire Wonders - Sigmund Bloom
Buy Low, Sell High - Bloom
WR/CB Matchups: Week 14 - Settle
Sharp Report: Week 14 - Zamichieli
- Hindery
Footballguys DFS Power Grid - Week 13 Main Slate - John Lee, Devin Knotts, Austin Lee, Phil Alexander
The Latest
Season Long Coverage: Week 14Daily Fantasy Coverage: Week 14The Replacements Week 14 - Waldman (12/11)DFS Coverage: Week 14 - Staff (12/11)Daily Email Update #237 (12/10)Buy Low, Sell High - Bloom (12/10)Week 14 Sleepers - Bloom (12/10)Week 14 TE Tiers - Bloom (12/10)Week 14 WR Tiers - Bloom (12/10)Week 14 RB Tiers - Bloom (12/10)OL Rankings - Bitonti (12/10)Week 14 QB Tiers - Bloom (12/10)2020 Season Long Coverage: Week 14 - Staff (12/10)Roundtable Week 14 - Staff (12/10)WR/CB Matchups: Week 14 - Settle (12/10)Monkey Knife Fight Player Props, Week 14 - Hindery (12/10)IDP Matchups: Week 14 - Larkin (12/10)Regression Alert: Week 14 - Harstad (12/10)#Trendspotting: Week 14 - Zamichieli (12/10)Injury Expectations | Midweek Update | Week 14 - Bramel (12/9)Passing Matchup Chart Week 14 - Staff (12/9)Sharp Report: Week 14 - Zamichieli (12/9)Rushing Matchup Chart Week 14 - Staff (12/9)Top 5 Passing Matchups Week 14 - Staff (12/9)Eliminator Pool: Week 14 - Pasquino (12/9)Bottom 5 Passing Matchups Week 14 - Staff (12/9)Top 5 Rushing Matchups Week 14 - Staff (12/9)Bottom 5 Rushing Matchups Week 14 - Staff (12/9)Daily Email Update #236 (12/9)IDP Matchup Tool - Rudnicki (12/9)Eyes of the Guru IDP Info, Week 14 - Norton (12/9)What You Need to Know From Week 13 - Bloom (12/9)2021 Talent Watchlist - Waldman (12/9)IDP Sleepers, Week 14 - Settle (12/9)Game Predictor: Week 14 - Dodds (12/9)3 Lessons Learned After Week 13 - Allen (12/9)For The Win: Week 14 - Larkin (12/9)Vegas Value Chart: Week 14 - Lee (12/8)Fantasy Overview - Week 14 - Haseley (12/8)Random Shots From Week 13 - Bryant (12/8)Normalized SOS: Week 14 - Lee (12/8)IDP Dynasty Sleepers, Week 14 - Tietgen (12/8)Lineup Dominator - Henderson (12/8)Trade Dominator - Henderson (12/8)Daily Email Update #235 (12/8)Rent-a-Kicker: Week 14 - Harstad (12/8)Rent-a-Defense - Bloom (12/8)Big Play Payday 14 - Simpkins (12/8)Dynasty Rankings Movement, Week 14 - Tefertiller (12/8)Cutting the Cord: Week 14 - Parsons (12/8)Monday Injury Rounds: Week 14 - Bramel (12/7)IDP Upgrades: Week 14 - Rudnicki (12/7)Dynasty News, Week 14 - Tefertiller (12/7)The Top 10: Week 14 - Waldman (12/7)Daily Email Update #234 (12/7)Waivers of the Future 14 - Simpkins (12/7)Daily Email Update #233 (12/6)2020 Season Long Coverage: Week 13 - Staff (12/6)New Reality: 2021 Free Agents - Parsons (12/5)Cracking FanDuel Week 13 - Knotts (12/5)Gameday Injury Expectations: Week 13 - Bramel (12/5)Daily Email Update #232 (12/5)Prop Talk Week 13 - Knotts (12/5)FanDuel GPP Guide: Week 13 - Hindery (12/4)DraftKings GPP Domination: Week 13 - Alexander (12/4)Daily Email Update #231 (12/4)Beating the Odds: Week 13 - Zamichieli (12/4)DFS Coverage: Week 13 - Staff (12/4)Week 13 TE Tiers - Bloom (12/3)Week 13 Sleepers - Bloom (12/3)Week 13 RB Tiers - Bloom (12/3)Buy Low, Sell High - Bloom (12/3)Eliminator Pool: Week 13 - Pasquino (12/3)Dynasty Trade Value Chart: December - Hindery (12/3)Top 5 Passing Matchups Week 13 - Staff (12/3)Top 5 Rushing Matchups Week 13 - Staff (12/3)Bottom 5 Passing Matchups Week 13 - Staff (12/3)Bottom 5 Rushing Matchups Week 13 - Staff (12/3)Rushing Matchup Chart Week 13 - Staff (12/3)Passing Matchup Chart Week 13 - Staff (12/3)Daily Email Update #230 (12/3)Week 13 WR Tiers - Bloom (12/3)O-Line Rankings: Week 13 - Bitonti (12/3)Week 13 QB Tiers - Bloom (12/3)Regression Alert: Week 13 - Harstad (12/3)The Replacements Week 13 - Waldman (12/3)WR/CB Matchups: Week 13 - Settle (12/3)Monkey Knife Fight: Week 13 - Hindery (12/3)Roundtable Week 13 - Staff (12/3)IDP Matchups: Week 13 - Larkin (12/3)For The Win: Week 13 - Larkin (12/3)#Trendspotting: Week 13 - Zamichieli (12/3)Sharp Report: Week 13 - Zamichieli (12/2)Injury Expectations | Midweek Update | Week 13 - Bramel (12/2)What You Need to Know From Week 12 - Bloom (12/2)Random Shots From Week 12 - Bryant (12/2)3 Lessons Learned After Week 12 - Allen (12/2)Daily Email Update #229 (12/2)Game Predictor: Week 13 - Dodds (12/2)IDP Sleepers, Week 13 - Settle (12/2)Big Play Payday: Week 13 - Simpkins (12/2)Tips and Picks - Lee (12/1) More Articles...
Hot Links
Articles
Depth Charts
Email Updates
Injury Blog
News
Podcasts
Projections
News Items Powered By:
